You may be seated. Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah.
Wow. I want to salute you.
Viewers all over the world, I salute your faith.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Wow. Viewers all over the world, I won't forget what you want me to talk about.
I can never forget it.
I can never forget it at all.
Oh my God!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You know that as your heart is in my heart,
the same way my heart - it is only you don't permit my heart in your heart.
Because of your complain now - you keep complaining.
There are a lot of things going on in your heart.
Hm, please, he should come and pray for me.
Don't worry. God is in control.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Well, last Sunday - how many of you came to the service last Sunday?
What a controversial service!
Will I call it like that?
Very controversial. That is to you.
The prophecy by itself was not controversial,
rather you, we - human beings.
Tell your neighbour:
The prophecy by itself was not controversial at all, rather we - human beings.
That is it.
It is not my problem; what is controversial there.
We have seen the outcome of the election in the United States.
Having seen and heard, you would notice that the prophecy was all about the popular vote -
the vote of the majority of people - Americans.
In this case, we need the spirit of a prophet to understand, know and recognise
what the prophet was talking about.
You know our levels are different.
Do you agree with that?
I said our levels are different.
We are not on the same level.
Take not of that: Our levels are different and we are not of the same level.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
That you have a very big cathedral, a huge bell and all kinds of activities
that are good by human standards,
remember, the human point of view is limited.
Let me take you to the Book of 1 Corinthians and see what it says there.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
1 Corinthians 1:25: "For the foolishness of God is wiser than human beings,
and the weakness of God is stronger than human strength."
That is, the foolishness of God, if there is, is wiser than that of man.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The weakness of God, if there is, is stronger than that of man.
There is no shortcut to spiritual maturity
unless earthly understanding gives way to spiritual enlightenment.
Many people were trying to interpret Prophet on the basis of their own minds and ideas.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I quite understand the prophecy actually caused uproar
to many who gave it a different meaning and interpretation.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Don't forget that politics, campaigns and elections in any democratic country are never about one person.
It is about the nation - the country we care for and love.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
It is about the country we care for and love, never about a person, the campaign and election.
If it is about the nation we care for and love, whatever happens,
we should accept the outcome and look to the future - Jesus, who is our future,
the Author and Finisher of our faith.
Don't forget, democracy is accommodation.
If democracy is accommodation, all democrats should value the process more than the product.
Do you know what I mean by process?
When I say look into the future - the Finisher and Author of our faith, that word is pregnant.
Who owns the future? - Jesus.
Jesus owns our future.
Whatever happens, we should accept it and look to the future.
Democracy is accommodation; it can accommodate anything.
You democrats should value the process more than the product.
I want to say to the nation of the United States, God bless you.
We will rise up and pray for the nation.
Whatever happens to that nation happens to the whole world.
Rise up for prayer.
Open your lips and ask God for the people of the United States and the world,
to accept the outcome and look to the future,
look to God - the Finisher and Author of our faith.
Prayer.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Overflow Congregation
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
To look to the future is to leave all to God; leave it for God.
Leave it for God and let's move on.
Since the logo of the United States is 'In God We Believe' - okay!
Say, In God We Believe!
If that is the logo - okay, let's look to God and leave the outcome.
Look to God and accept the outcome.
God bless you, United States. Thank you.
You may be seated.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If I show you some emails, you will be shocked.
Can you get me just one of those emails, out of thousands of emails.
Let them bring it.
People's faith...
It is true that in Africa, we have churches everywhere.
We have churches everywhere; every home is a church.
But that does not mean that we have more faith than other continents that don't have churches everywhere.
That we have churches everywhere does not mean that we have faith.
If I may say something to you: the prophecy I gave here last Sunday -
thousands of people went for fasting and prayer, telling God and crying.
I will show you one of their leaders.
Crying to God that "God, please hear our cry! We want this thing to change!"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thousands. They did not hide it - they called and said, "Thank you, Man of God.
Thank you. You have awoken us.
We heard your prophecy and immediately, we called each other.
Thousands or so went to the wilderness to fast and pray - naked - we prayed to God, 'Change this!'"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You know, I don't want to talk too much. I just leave it.
You know, what I just told you about, I had just read it.
I will take one out of the thousand emails I received.
"Change this!"
They said, "Thank you. Your prophecy gave us a clue and guideline.
Change this, Lord! Help us, Lord!"
Fasting and prayer.
If I said to my brother here, "Hey, brother!
Two of you are looking for the position of chairman of the company.
But I'm seeing you being taken. Indeed, your name is on the table.
And the time to call you to become a chairman is in the next three days".
If the person, your second, heard me, maybe he is not in the church here but outside there sitting down,
maybe he is in another country and sees your face,
he may naked himself and say, "God, I want this position!
God, forgive me my sins - whatever I have done!"
Don't be surprised when he may be taken and you may not be taken.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I repeat again.
If two of you are looking for the position of a chairman of a company
and I call you out and say, "Oh, your paper is on the table now - right now!
The most qualified!"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If the person that is also looking for that position is somewhere watching us,
don't surprised that if the person also has the heart of God,
he may naked himself that moment and say, "Lord, save this situation!
I am naked before You. Forgive me whatever I might have done.
Do it for me, Lord!"
Don't be surprised if you don't stand steadfast, his prayer may be answered.
That may not make a prophet a prophet of doom.
Take note of that.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Have you found it? Give me.
This is one out of the cartons.
Maybe after this, I will ask them to bring all the emails out.
Not only the emails - their pictures are there.
It is not a fake email.
This is one out of thousands of emails.
I will show you the picture at a distance.
See the picture.
Do you see the picture?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Somebody who can read clearly, can you please help us to read this email
and you will be able to read it fluently.
Okay. Don't open the picture. Just read the email.
'America Saved Because Prophet Warned Us!' from Malta
Thursday, 10 November 2016
We love you, Prophet.
Thank you for helping save America.
Your word sent us into deep prayer, fasting and weeping for America.
God heard and spared us. Thank you.
Prophet T.B. Joshua, you were not wrong; it was a strong warning.
Perhaps it is like Jonah who was to prophesy that Nineveh would be destroyed
because of their wickedness.
But the people repented and turned to God and prayed
and they were spared from the destruction that God had decreed.
We love you, Prophet.
Thank you for helping save America.
Your word sent us into deep prayer, fasting and weeping for America.
God heard and spared us. Thank you.
Prophet T.B. Joshua, you were not wrong; it was a strong warning.
Perhaps it is like Jonah who was to prophesy that Nineveh would be destroyed
because of their wickedness.
But the people repented and turned to God and prayed
and they were spared from the destruction that God had decreed.
Christians, not only in the U.S. but in the whole world, prayed.
After hearing your prophecy, we cried, fasted and prayed from Sunday -
through 5am to Wednesday morning, to assure Trump would win.
Prophet, God heard our prayers.
We cried out to God for mercy and grace on America.
We need His guidance, not even influence. We fasted and prayed...
Okay, it is alright.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
This is one out of thousands.
Now, you know I read this thing twice.
The first one I read, I didn't want to mention it.
I said the person will win narrowly.
But the fear I have, which I said, is that the boat will be rocked.
And I said there will be challenges - great ones.
To 'rock the boat' means there will be crises.
Look - I'm just a servant.
That we will look at what God has written somewhere -
even sometimes, when God is not there, maybe God is not there,
you know when your master has written something on a paper,
and he is not there, maybe he is somewhere,
we servants sometimes run - "Oh!"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
And the person that has written it is not just a common person - he is a Dr, PhD, Professor and a Pastor.
He is a professor.
He is one of the leaders.
They said that what I saw was true but they were doubting it.
But they know my antecedent - my track record.
That when this man says something, it is like that oo! Ah!
Okay, what we were doubting before, this man has said it oo!
Let's go and die before God!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
They said they will write a book - a full book - and send it to me.
I just laughed.
This is the power of prayer for you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Just a servant.
Is it a crime to tell you what is before you?
It is not a crime to tell you, "Look, I'm seeing you there".
It is not a crime; it is a time to say, "Ey!"
and give your heart...
It is not a crime.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I remember one time - that was eight years ago.
I said there is a plane that will be leaving the tarmac.
I think the head of the aviation then - a very godly man -
in fact, I had not finished the service when he called.
He said, "Man of God, where? Is it this place? No plane will move for now till tomorrow".
I had to draw the mic because they said somebody was on the line.
I said, "Hello, sir".
He said, "This tarmac?
No no no - unless a plane that is coming. No plane will...
Is it the one coming or the one that will move?"
I said, "The one that will move".
He said, "From today till tomorrow afternoon, no plane will move".
And indeed - that happened just like that and nobody ever knew.
So, there are some people that have this...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Let us believe the power of prayer.